localads.co.uk 2019-02-25

# Justlooking - Deals, Discounts, Vouchers & Money Saving Tips

**Data Protection and Privacy Policy**

Justlooking.com is treats member’s privacy very seriously and we do all that we can to ensure that the data held on our members is protected and used correctly. We will do our utmost to protect your information but cannot guarantee the security of the data you submit to our website or our app; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures to try to prevent unauthorised access.

Justlooking.com contains links to third party stores and websites. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies. It is your responsibility to check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

In order to register for our service, we only require an email address (and a password). For rewards we require additional information in order to be able to confirm recipient and account for payments made.

Prior to sending any payments, we will also require details in order to make payment – this may be in the form of BACS details or a registered Paypal email address. We also keep accounts updated with rewards earnt based on your activity via the Justlooking website. In order to track the rewards, we keep a record of your activity.

We will never pass on information about you unless we are legally obliged to do so. We will never use any of your data in ways that have unjustified adverse effects on you.

On rare occasions personal data may also be disclosed if we are requested to do so by law, or receive a valid request for its disclosure – for example fraud prevention measures. Details passed on will not be used for marketing or any other purposes.

Justlooking may use data on your click behaviour to send/display deals which we believe will be of interest to you. You can opt out of receiving these communications within your account settings.

**Emails and Correspondence**

If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. If you opt in to our newsletters and alerts, you will receive correspondence from us to this email address. You can opt in or out of alerts through your profile settings and via the “unsubscribe” link in newsletters. We will never pass on your email to third parties.

**Commenting on the Forum**

You are wholly responsible for what you post on the forums. We advise against posting personal information or pictures or anything that could identify you as an individual on Justlooking. We recommend not using sensitive information when creating usernames, you’re responsible for ensuring you keep your sign in information private.

**Cookies**

We may analyse details of your visits to our site or your use of the app, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data and other communication data and the resources that you access.

Websites use cookies to make the browsing experience more efficient, and to help you use websites to their full potential. Cookies are a small text file that is transferred to your hard drive or the internal memory of your mobile device.

**What do our cookies do?**

They help you to personalise your experience with our site, allowing you to engage with the Justlooking community fully. Our cookies enable you to vote, comment, earn rewards, link to the correct bay and stay signed in while you browse the site. Additionally they allow us to track affiliate activity. Some merchants pay commission when you go to their site from Justlooking.

Our cookies do not share any of your personal data with us, and we would never use any information derived from cookies to try to identify anybody. We will never share any data with third parties.

We believe that the cookies used are strictly necessary to offer the services/provision of rewards and related services and are non-intrusive used to enhance the service offered

By using Justlooking, you agree to the guidelines set out in our privacy policy. To find out more about how this works or you are concerned about this, please visit http://www.youronlinechoices.eu.

**Contact**

As part of our compliance with the Data Protection Act 1998, we give members the opportunity to view any information held on them as an individual. This may include account totals, contact details and other information.

Questions, comments and requests regarding this policy can be requested by using our ‘Contact Us’ form. There may be a small administration fee for requesting this information, which will be no more than £5.
